Alright, let's do another exercise of matching information,
but now it is in section 3.
This exercise has 5 questions, we are going
to read the requirements, all the questions and
options and then underline the keywords.
Firstly, in the question, what decision do the
students make about each of the following parts
of their presentation, we have some keywords like
what decision students make parts of their presentation,
all the options are the keywords and we
have to think of paraphrases of them.
For example, option A, use visual can be
paraphrased as use maps and pictures.
Option B, keep it short can be replaced
by be concise.
Option C, involve other students can be rewritten
as ask other students.
Option D, check if the information is accurate
can be paraphrased as verify the information.
Option E, provide a handout can be replaced
with give a handout.
Option F, focus on one example can be
paraphrased as only analyse one case.
Option G, do online research can be rewritten
as look on the internet.
Step 3, for matching information in section 3,
when listening you have to draw a table
to take notes.
The number of columns corresponds to the number
of speakers.
Next, you will listen to the recording and
answer the questions in the practice section and
don't forget to check your answers as usual.
Keep up the great work and see you
soon.